A Guide to the Rives-Barclay Family Papers, 1698-1941
Library of Virginia
- Oversize (Box 20 and Map Case G-14/Drawer 10)
  The oversize items include deeds, estate papers, newspapers, passports of George L. Rives, promissory notes, a family register of the Whiting family, the wills of George Anthony Aufrere, Susan Barclay, Oliver DeLancey, Mary Huguetan de Gastine, and John Norris, and miscellaneous items.
  - Deeds, 1794-1832 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Estate Papers of George Anthony Aufrere (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Estate Papers of Stephen DeLancey (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Newspapers (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Passports of George L. Rives, 1870, 1871 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Promissory Notes of R. and G.L. Schulyer (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Whiting Family Register, 1762-1873 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Will of George Anthony Aufrere (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Will of Susan Barclay (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Will of John Norris (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Will of Mary Huguetan de Gastine, 1698 (French and English)
  - Will of Oliver DeLancey, 1774
  - Deed, Abraham Willson & wife to James A. Stewart, 1796